NYS PERB Agreements 5140
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
NYS PERB Agreements
2000-2014
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State Public Employment Relations Board (PERB)
5140
406.17 cubic feet
405.2 linear ft.
Records (documents), collective labor agreements, cd-roms, arbitration files, case files, correspondence.
Collective bargaining agreements between unions and public employers in New York State.
5555844
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, August 13, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 07, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The Public Employment Relations Board (PERB) is responsible for assisting in resolving labor-relations disputes between public-employee organizations and agencies of State and local government and school districts. PERB provides mediation, fact-finding, and arbitration services in disputes over contract agreements; it settles questions of union representation; and it hears charges of improper practices by public employers, employees, and employee organizations.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3001: Jean T. McKelvey Papers /3012: Alice Cook Papers /4039: Milton R. Konvitz Papers /4057: James A. Gross NLRB Files /4057 P: James A. Gross NLRB Photographs /4079: James A. Gross Additional Files /4124: James A. Gross Papers, Additional NLRB Research Files /4190: James A. Gross Additional Research Files /4212: Kheel Center Current Documents Correspondence /4232: James A. Gross Collection of NLRB 60th Annual Conference Files /4283: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Files /4335: Jean T. McKelvey Collections /4349: James A. Gross Collections 5281: Arnold Zack Arbitration Files 5512: Arnold Zack Arbitration Files 5541: Philip Taft Papers 5551: Arnold M. Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5583/2: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2 5583/5: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5 5583/6: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 6 5620: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5659: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5727: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5786: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5825: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5861: Arnold M. Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5913: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5950: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Cases 5959: James A. Gross Additional Arbitration Files 5960: E. Wight Bakke Additional Papers 5979: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 6047: Archives Information File 6066: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 6104: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 6141: Arnold Zack Arbitration Files 6174/004: NYSUT Field Services Department Files 6250: Arnold M. Zack Additional Arbitration Files 6366: Eric W. Lawson Arbitration Files
Unfair labor practices -- New York (State); Arbitration, Industrial -- New York (State); Collective bargaining -- Government employees -- New York (State); Strikes and lockouts -- Civil service -- New York (State); Employee-management relations in government -- New York (State); Collective bargaining -- New York (State); Government employee unions -- New York (State); New York (State) -- Officials and employees; New York (State). Public Employment Relations Board.
5555844
- Boards of Education: Abbott through Adirondack (Box 1)
  - Abbott, 1997-2001 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abbott School, 1988-1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Adams Center, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Addison, 1989-1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Addison, 1974-1983 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Addison, 1972-1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Addison Central School, 1971-1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Adirondack, 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Adirondack, 1976-1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Adirondack, 1988-1998 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Adirondack, 1989-1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Boards of Education: Afton through Albany (Box 2)
  - Afton, 1973-2002 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Afton, 1971-1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Afton, 1983-1996 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Afton, 1969-1972 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Akron, 1970-1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Akron School District, 1992-2000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Akron, 1968-1981 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Akron, 1968-2002 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Albany, 1989-1997 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Albany, 1972-1984 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Albany-Schenectady-Scoharie, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Albany, 1969-1988 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Albany, 1969-2002 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Boards of Education: Albion through Alexander (Box 3)
  - Alexander School District, 1996-2000 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Albion C.S. School District, 1989-2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Albion, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Albion, 1981-1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Albion, 1968-1986 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Albion, 1973-1996 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Alden, 1971-1984 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Alden School District, 1990-1999 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Alden, 1969-2004 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Alden, 1972-2000 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Alexander, 1970-1996 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Alexander, 1970-2000 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Alexander, 1971-1984 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Boards of Education: Alexandria through Altmar-Parish Williamston (Box 4)
  - Alexandria Central, 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Alexandria School District, 1993-2002 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Alexandria Central School, 1982-2004 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Alden, 1974-1996 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Alfred-Almond, 1969-1988 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Alfred-Almond School District, 1977-2001 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Alfred-Almond, 1992-1999 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Alfred-Almond, 1977-2008 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Allegany CSD, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Allegany School District, 1995-2003 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Allegany, 1969-1982 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Allegany, 1971-1988 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Allegany, 1990-2000 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Altona, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Altmar- Parish - Williamstown, 1971-1992 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Altmar, Parish, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Altman - Parish - Williamstown, 1989-1996 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Altman - Parish - Williamstown, 1993-2003 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Boards of Education: Altmar-Paris Williamston through Amityville (Box 5)
  - Altman - Parish - Williamstown, 1973-2000 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Amagansett P.S., 1992-1996 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Amagansett, 1970-1986 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Amagansett, 1974-1979 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Amagansett, 1986-1992 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Amherst, 1986-1998 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Amherst School District, 1994-2002 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Amherst, 1970-1977 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Amherst, 1973-1992 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Amherst, 1968-1997 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Amityville, 1977-1993 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Amityville, 1974-1983 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Amityville, 1975-1988 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Amityville, 1988-1996 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Amityville School District, 1985-1999 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Amityville, 1970-1984 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Boards of Education: Amityville through Ardsley (Box 6)
  - Amityville, 1970-1988 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Amsterdam, 1978-1983 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Amsterdam, 1973-1984 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Andes CSD, 1992-1995 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Andes, 1987-1990 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Andover, 1972-1994 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Andover, 1971-2003 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Andover S.D., 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Andover, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Andrew S. Draper, 1972-1981 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Angelica, 1968-1997 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Angelica C.S. School District, 1990-1995 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Angelica, 1972-1994 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Angelica, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Angelica, 1986-1989 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Archdiocesan Association of Parish Elementary and Parish Secondary Schools, 1969-1971 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Ardsley, 1968-1972 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Ardsley, 1986-1995 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Ardsley, 1969-1983 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Ardsley, 1970-2004 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Ardsley, 1980-1997 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Boards of Education: Ardsley through Armonk (Box 7)
  - Ardsley P.S. School District, 1992-2001 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Ardsley, 1972-1993 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Argyle, 1987-1993 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Argyle School District, 1991-1996 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Argyle, 1972-1996 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Argyle, 1970-1981 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Arkport, 1968-1984 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Arkport, 1968-1973 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Arkport School District, 1989-1995 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Arkport, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Arkport, 1972-1991 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Arlington, 1968-1985 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Arlington, 1982-2005 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Arlington, 1970-1983 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Arlington School Districts, 1994-2001 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Armonk, 1974-1987 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Boards of Education: Attica through Auburn (Box 8)
  - Attica, 1973-1988 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Attica, 1968-1992 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Attica, 1968-1995 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Attica, 1973-1985 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Attica C.S. School District, 1989-1995 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Auburn, 1973-1988 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Auburn, 1988-1997 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Auburn, 1970-1992 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Auburn, 1970-1983 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Auburn C.S.D. School District, 1991-2001 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Auburn, 1976-1994 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Boards of Education: Ausable through Avon (Box 9)
  - Ausable, 1986-2003 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Ausable, 1972-1994 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Ausable, 1968-1993 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Averill Park Central School District, 1996-2007 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Averill Park, 1971-1976 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Averill Park, 1968-1978 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Averill Park, 1972-1992 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Avoca, 1970-1982 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Avoca C.S. School District, 1991-2002 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Avoca, 1968-1994 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Avon, 1977-1986 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Avon, 1986-1993 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Avon, 1970-1983 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Avon CSD, 1993-2005 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Avon, 1970-1977 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Boards of Education: Babylon through Baldwin (Box 10)
  - Babylon U.F.S.D School District, 1993-2003 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Babylon, 1969-1983 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Babylon, 1985-1993 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Babylon, 1976-1985 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Babylon, 1968-1996 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Babylon, 1972-1990 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Bainbridge-Guilford, 1988-2004 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Bainbridge-Guilford, 1971-1994 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Baldwin, 1970-1980 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Baldwin U.F.S.D., 1984 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Baldwin, 1973-1983 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Baldwin U.F.S.D., 1994-2004 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Baldwin, 1970-1993 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Baldwin, 1968-1991 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Boards of Education: Baldwin through Ballston Spa (Box 11)
  - Ballston Spa, 1970-1989 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Balston Spa, 1973-1990 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Ballston Spa, 1985-2004 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Barker Central School District, 1993-2001 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Barker, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Barker, 1977-1994 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Barker, 1970-1998 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Batavia, 1971-1984 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Batavia City School District, 1992-1999 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Boards of Education: Ballston Spa through Batavia (Box 12)
  - Baldwin, 1968-2002 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Baldwinsville, 1968-1991 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Baldwin, 1986-2001 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Baldwin, 1985-1996 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Baldwinsville, 1983-2002 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Baldwinsville, 1970-1979 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Baldwinsville School District, 1986-2005 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Ballston Spa, 1970-1982 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Ballston Spa - School District, 1986-1997 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Ballston Spa, 1973-1989 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Boards of Education: Bath through Bayshore (Box 13)
  - Bath SD, 1989-2008 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Bath, 1997-2000 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Batavia, 1968-1979 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Batavia, 1970-1992 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Bayport - Blue Point, 1970-1994 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Bayport - Blue Point, 1984-1992 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Bayport - Blue Point Board of Education, 1991-2002 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Bayport - Bluepoint Office Personnel, 1981-1982 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Bayport - Bluepoint, 1972-1993 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Bayshore, 1972-1991 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Bay shore, 1970-1999 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Boards of Education: Bayshore through Bedford (Box 14)
  - Bay shore, 1970-1980 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Bay Shore P.S., 1990-1997 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Bay Shore, 1984-1995 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Bayville - Brookville - Locust Valley, 1968-1973 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Beacon, 1986-1989 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Beacon City School District, 1969-1993 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Beacon, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Beacon School District, 1989-2001 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Beacon, 1968-1992 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Beaver River School District, 1992-1994 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Beaver River, 1989-1992 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Beaver River, 1975-2007 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Beaver River, 1968-1987 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Bedford, 1973-1990 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Bedford, 1986-1995 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Bedford, 1991-1996 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Bedford, 1970-1980 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Boards of Education: Bedford through Belleville (Box 15)
  - Bedford, 1968-1992 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Beekmantown, 1969-1974 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Beekmantown School District, 1991-2005 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Beekmantown, 1968-1991 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Beekmantown, 1974-1991 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Beekmantown, 1981-1997 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Belmont School District, 1991-1996 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Belfast, 1974-2003 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Belfast, 1970-2000 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Belleville CSD, 1994-2001 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Belleville Central School, 1970-1999 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Belleville, 1972-1994 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Belleville - Henderson, 1983-1994 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Bellesville, 1969-1987 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Boards of Education: Bellemore through Belmont (Box 16)
  - Bellmore U.F.S.D. School District, 1990-1996 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Bellmore-Merrick CHSD, 1991-2003 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Bellmore, 1969-1996 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Bellmore, 1971-2000 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Bellmore, 1968-1976 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Bellmore - Merrick, 1968-1991 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Bellmore - Merrick, 1973-2002 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Bellmore, 1972-1995 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Bellport, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Bellport, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Bellport, 1970-1988 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Belmont, 1969-1984 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Belmont, 1989-1991 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Belmont, 1970-1972 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Belmont, 1972-1989 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Boards of Education: Bemus Point through Bethlehem (Box 17)
  - Bemus Point, 1968-1993 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Bemus Point, 1988-1997 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Bemus Point School District, 1997-2004 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Berne-Knox-Westerlo, 1970-1999 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Berne-Knox, 1970-1980 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Berne-Knox, 1969-1982 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Berne-Knox, 1968-1982 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Berne Knox C.S., 1990-1994 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Berlin C.S. School District, 1993-2001 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Berlin, 1987-1996 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Berlin, 1968-1984 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Berlin Central School District, 1996-1999 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Berlin CSD, 1977-1982 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Berkshire, 1968-1989 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Berkshire, 1993-1995 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Berkshire Farm, 1990-1994 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Berkshire Farm For Boys UFSD, 1995-1998 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Berkshire, 1974-1979 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Berkshire Farm, 1971-1974 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Berkshire, 1974-1993 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Bethlehem, 1972-1984 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Bethlehem, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Bethlehem C.S.D., 1989-1996 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Bethlehem, 1970-2001 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Boards of Education: Bethlehem through Binghamton (Box 18)
  - Bethlehem, 1972-1984 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Bethlehem, 1968-1995 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Bethpage, 1972-1987 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Bethpage, 1968-1994 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Bethpage, 1977-1989 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Bethpage, 1970-1988 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Bethpage School District, 1991-1995 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Bethpage, 1975-1996 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Binghamton, 1968-1989 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Binghamton, 1971-1985 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Binghamton City School District, 1995-2003 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Boards of Education: Binghamton through Bloomfield (Box 19)
  - Binghamton, 1973-1987 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Binghamton, 1987-1997 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Blind Brook, 1987-1994 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Blind Brook - Rye UFSD, 1995-2005 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Blind Brook Rye, 1975-1998 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Bloomfield, 1972-1999 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Bloomfield, 1968-1978 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Boards of Education: BOCES Allegany County through BOCES Cattarugus-Erie-Wyoming (Box 20)
  - BOCES (Cattaungus-Erie-Wyoming), 1972-1992 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - BOCES (Cattunga-Erie-Wyoming), 1970-1972 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - BOCES (Broome-Delaware-Tioga), 1972-2003 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - BOCES (Broome-Tioga-Delaware Counties), 1971 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - BOCES (Broome-Delaware-Tioga Employees), 1981 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - BOCES (Broome-Delaware-Tioga), 1997-2003 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - BOCES (Broome-Delaware-Tioga), 1986-2006 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - BOCES (Broome-Delaware-Tioga), 1968-1997 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - BOCES (Albany-Schoharie-Schenectady), 1973-2000 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - BOCES (Albany-Schoharie-Schenectady), 1988-1995 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - BOCES (Allegany County), 1972-1978 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - BOCES, 1994-2006 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Boards of Education: BOCES Cattaraugus-Erie-Wyoming through BOCES Cortland (Box 21)
  - BOCES (Cattaungus-Erie-Wyoming), 1981-1992 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - BOCES (Cattarangus Co.), 1971 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - BOCES (Cattarangus-Erie-Wyoming), 1990-1995 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - BOCES (Cattaraugus-Allegany-Erie-Wyoming Counties), 1985-2001 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - BOCES (Cayuga County), 1972-1989 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - BOCES (Cayuga-Onondaga), 1989-1999 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - BOCES (Cayuga Co), 1968-1981 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - BOCES (Cayuga-Onondaga), 1997-2000 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - BOCES (Chautaugua Co), 1971-1985 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - BOCES (Chautauqua), 1982-1999 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Chemung-Tioga Vocational, 1969-1970 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - BOCES (Clinton-Essex-Warren-Washington), 1986-1995 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - BOCES (Clinton, Essex, Warren, Washington), 1991-2004 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - BOCES (Clinton, Essex, Warren, Washington), 1971-2006 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - BOCES (Cortland-Madison), 1972-1983 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - BOCES (Cortland-Madison), 1977-1983 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - BOCES (Cortland-Madison), 1983-1985 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - BOCES Cortland, 1969-1981 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - BOCES (Cortland-Onondaga-Madison), 1978-1996 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Boards of Education: BOCES Delaware-Chenango-Madison-Otsego through BOCES Erie (Box 22)
  - BOCES (Delaware, Chenango, Madison, Otsego), 1972-1980 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - BOCES (Delaware-Chenango-Madison-Otsego), 1993-1998 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - BOCES (Delaware, Chenango, Madison, Otsego), 1971-1993 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - BOCES (Delaware, Chenango, Madison, Otsego), 1980-1995 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - BOCES (Dutchess County), 1969-1972 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - BOCES (Dutchess Co), 1972-1987 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - BOCES (Dutchess) School District, 1987-1993 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - BOCES (Dutchess County), 1969-1984 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - BOCES (Dutchess County), 2006 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - BOCES Erie School District, 1987-2002 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - BOCES (Erie Co), 1971-1985 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - BOCES (Erie County), 1972-1991 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - BOCES Erie School District, 1997-2002 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - BOCES (Erie County), 1969-1995 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - BOCES (Erie-Cattauraugus), 1982-1995 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - BOCES (Erie, Chatauqua, Cattaraugus), 1990-1997 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Boards of Education: BOCES Franklin through BOCES Herkimer (Box 23)
  - BOCES (Franklin, Hamilton, Essex), 1979-1983 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - BOCES (Franklin, Hamilton, Essex), 1995-2003 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - BOCES (Franklin), 1977-1990 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - BOCES (Franklin, Essex, Hamilton), 1989-2002 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Genesee, Livingston, Steuben, Wyoming, 1998-2004 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Genesee Wyoming, 1968-1990 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Genesee-Wyoming (BOCES), 1973-1988 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Genesee-Wyoming (BOCES), 1991-1997 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Genesee-Wyoming (BOCES), 1972-1991 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - BOCES (Greene County), 1972-1985 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - BOCES (Greene Co), 1970-1974 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Greene, Delaware, Schoharie, Otsego, 1968-1997 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Franklin, Essex, Hamilton, 1992-2002 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - BOCES (Hamilton-Fulton-Montgomery), 1975-2009 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - BOCES (Hamilton-Fulton-Montgomery), 1974-1980 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - BOCES (Hamilton-Fulton-Montgomery), 1968-1987 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - BOCES (Hamilton-Fulton-Montgomery), 1987-1990 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - BOCES (Herkimer-Fulton-Hamilton), 1972-1992 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Herkimer County, 1971-1992 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - BOCES (Herkimer County), 1988-1994 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - BOCES (Herkimer County), 1974-1995 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Boards of Education: BOCES Jefferson through BOCES Monroe-Orleans (Box 24)
  - BOCES (Jefferson Co), 1971-1977 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - BOCES (Jefferson-Hamilton-Herkimer-Oneida), 1997-2001 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - BOCES (Jefferson, Lewis, Hamilton, Herkimer, Oneida), 1976-2006 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - BOCES (Jefferson-Lewis-Hamilton-Herkimer-Oneida), 1988-2004 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - BOCES (Jefferson-Lewis), 1974-1992 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Jefferson County, 1971-1974 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - BOCES (Lewis County), 1973 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - BOCES (Lewis County), 1972-1974 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - BOCES (Lewis), 1969-1995 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - BOCES (Livingston-Steuben-Wyoming), 1972-1987 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - BOCES (Livingston-Steuben-Wyoming), 1974-1983 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - BOCES (Livingston-Steuben-Wyoming), 1986-1993 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - BOCES (Livingston-Steuben), 1970-1991 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - BOCES (Livingston-Steuben-Wyoming), 1987-1994 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - BOCES (Madison, Oneida), 1970-1986 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - BOCES (Madison, Oneida), 1972-1991 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - BOCES (Madison, Oneida), 1985-1998 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - BOCES (Madison-Oneida), 1996-2000 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - BOCES Monroe, 2003-2006 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - BOCES Monroe First Supervisory District, 2002-2005 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - BOCES Monroe, 1974-2000 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - BOCES (Monroe-Orleans), 1982 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - BOCES (Monroe-Orleans), 1985 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - BOCES (Monroe-Orleans), 1993-1996 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Boards of Education: BOCES Monroe-Orleans through BOCES Orange-Ulster (Box 25)
  - BOCES Monroe, 1971-1997 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - BOCES (Nassau County), 1982-2004 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - BOCES Nassau, 1983-2005 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - BOCES Nassau, 1973-1981 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - BOCES Nassau, 1989-1995 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - BOCES Nassau, 1969-1996 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - BOCES Oneida-Madison-Herkimer, 1972-1996 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - BOCES Oneida-Madison-Herkimer, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 8)